So here its headlight is
completely broken, friend, look, we have to suffer due to the mistake of others,
whatever the cost will be, we will have to pay for it
brother, look, this was,
look, there will be a major damage file charge, if it is done,
fine, if it is not done then we will talk about it, let me
tell you what the
process is, look, our bike has been
surveyed, after six days it took some
days for the insurance
claim, so now let's talk
about our bike in detail, so look, it is
necessary to get PPF done on these also
[Music]
these are all the old parts, look, let me
show you what it is and look, all this
stuff has come out,
hello, how are you all, this is Vivek
and today is not a normal blog, today
look, the bike has met with a small accident which happened
yesterday, so look, this is, here
its headlight is completely broken and look, the
entire assembly is gone from here, its mudguard is gone,
our PPF has also come out from here,
friend, now look, it is completely gone, I
mean, on the side, in this  There are scratches
everywhere, you must be seeing them here, there is a
scratch on the left side, on the handlebar,
here is this scratch, etc., look,
all this is there, nothing happened to the rest of the mechanical part, it is
good that the bike is safe, nothing happened
here, its indicator is also damaged, so
see, this is not burning, now the right one is burning,
but the left one is not burning, the rear one is
burning, look, the rear one is burning, okay, so
look, now you can see it
clearly here, here is the damage, so the damage is
quite big, prominent, the rest of
our levers are saved, there is a small scratch here,
here also it is small, that is, this bar end,
our small tank is also a little bit, so
our PPF saved it,
look, here a small bike, there
is a big scratch, now let's go to the survey center and I will
show you whatever process etc. is there, okay,
so now let's go to the company once
and I will show you a little, that is, the
damage in this, look, there is some damage,
our headlight is broken, see completely, that is, the
inside unit is not broken, only
our outside glass is  It's completely broken
and look, ours is damaged here, there are
scratches on some panels on the other side,
you can see there are scratches here,
this indicator is not
working and there are scratches here, I
mean, the major damage is mostly on the
left side, let's go
to the agency once and talk about the claim,
because now I will definitely file a claim for this
because this damage is
major, if the damage was a little less,
I would have got it done from outside, but look friend, and
yes, there is one thing I forgot to tell you,
our handlebar is also slightly
bent, if you look here, there is
no gap, the
alignment of the bike is also a little bad, so that's why
I want it to be
shown to the company, it will be better to go there,
so let's go, let's go to the company and let's go to the
center first and I will show you what all the
processes etc. are involved in
insurance claims, right,
so let's always go to our
insurance company, which is from the company  In that,
our first party insurance is valid for one year
and the remaining four years are for
our third party
insurance, if there is damage of about 50 percent of the bike's IDV,
then
our company
puts it in total loss,
okay, but in our case, there is
no system of total loss in this, and if we
talk about the rest of the insurance, then I
currently have insurance from ICICI Bank,
which the company had given, so
we will get the benefit of this, the advantage of the company's
insurance is that
you do not have to make many rounds
because the surveyor is of the company itself,
so he is there, so the clip that you
saw earlier, I had made it
yesterday because I had gone there yesterday also, but
yesterday was our Republic Day, so yesterday
our service center was closed, something is getting stuck
in the front wheel, I do
n't know what it is, I will have to
show it, I have
figured it out properly, but I did
not get it, I am feeling a bit strange
That friend, this is the condition of my brand new bike,
I never wanted my bike to be in this
condition, friend, look, we have to suffer because of other's mistake,
now you know friend, look, they do
n't drive properly at all,
because of that such a huge loss has happened, now I do
n't know friend, this way the bike will be able to be repaired
or not and at the time
of the accident, my elder brother was riding it, I
mean, elder brother used to pick it up from the office, when
he was returning, this happened to him,
so by the grace of God, there was
not much damage to it, just a little
scratches on the fingers and the
rest can you see,
brother, it is slightly moving towards the left, if we
leave the steering or the handle bar, then the
bike is slightly moving towards the left,
or it is an issue because the impact on the bike was
high and this is my first
time when I am making a claim, I have
not made an insurance claim till date, so I do
n't have that much experience of it, but at night I did a lot of accidents  You have
seen the videos in which I mean to make a claim,
what all processes are involved in it,
so today your brother should go with full confidence that
whatever happens will be seen, so this is our showroom
from where I bought the bike and by going to its side
you will find its service center inside, so
if we go from here, take a left from here, so
this is the service center because a lot of
people had asked in the service video
that brother, from where did you get it serviced, so
see brother, I have revealed this location,
okay, so now we have come here
[praise] let
me show you what is there inside it, okay, okay, we have reached the center and look, this is our bike, right, and here is the service center piece, now we have to go from here to the third floor, let me show you whatever process
etc., okay,
brother, let's say bye to our bike,
now we will meet after about 10 days, so
brothers, we have left the bike, now let's
see how much time it takes in it,
and I have told you three-four things, see, I found
some additional things in it, let's see
How many times do I get it
so soon or I hope it gets done quickly,
I was saying that there was a lot of damage, I mean, it was a
lot, when we were checking it, we
saw that there is a lot of damage on our alloy, I
mean, you have a photo here,
you must be seeing it, there is a lot of damage on the alloy as
well, there is a lot of damage on the left
suspension, it is on top of that, so I mean, there is a lot of damage,
I have not paid anything yet,
we will have to pay
in the end, there will be only a file charge of ₹5000000
and whatever expenses are incurred, I will have to pay for it in 10 days, okay, so
now I will
tell you what all
processes are there, so if we talk about the process, then the
photocopy of our owner's PAN card, his Aadhar card and his DL has to be submitted, along with that
you have to mention the accident place plus accident time,
where did your accident happen, where did it happen
and what caused it, that is, you have to write a complete statement  The
rest is really
not that much of a problem, it gets done easily,
I mean, look, I am talking about my
TVS and I don't
know about the brand, all right, so right now I am sitting here, I
came again today and right now,
look, I am going to
ask him for approval, I mean, our bike has been
surveyed and the bike is standing in front of me, there is no
progress as well
but the approval has come, so right now I will
ask him what changes need to be made in it
and whatever it is, I will tell him
first, I am calling him, brother,
look, our bike is parked like this, there was a lot of damage to the city, hey,
look, he has gone inside, he will
ask, he will show the report,
I will show it to you also, what all has
come in the report, yes, your headlight will not be installed, okay, okay, there is
one lamp, this mask is complete, there is a
headlight too, yes, yes, this is a lamp, no, I
mean, this one will also be there, in this all the
different parts, this is separate, this is separate, the
headlight is separate, this is a separate headlight,
okay, okay, this one is there  It will
open and get aligned, there will be no change,
if the alignment is done, it is okay, if it is not done
then we will talk to the company and get the new one
approved, one, this one is okay, okay,
this tank cover of yours is done, this is a
complete change, yes okay, okay, the leg guard has been
changed, yes okay, the
handle has been done, only the left one, that is,
both the left ones have been completely changed, from here till here, okay okay,
your indicator is done, okay okay, yes,
your lever is done, this one is done, this damper is done, okay okay, okay,
and this is the
front front mudguard, that wheel wheel
wheel has also changed, yes and the mudguard is good,
yes okay, okay, show me this once,
take a photo of it, yes absolutely take it, come on brother,
see, our approval has come, quite good,
means it is correct, maximum things have to be
replaced in it, our headlight will be
replaced in it, our visor will change,
complete indicator will be taken, handle bar will
change completely, this also means the bar end will be completely
changed, our cover at the back, the
handle, that has to be changed, has to be changed
Our wheel in the front has to be changed, inside it there will be a
mudguard, I have told you, there will also be a side tank
panel and this is our leg guard, so
all these changes are there in it,
around 10, there are around two or ten changes, or
10 parts are in place, now
we will receive it after two days, I will come here after two or three days to
receive it, okay okay okay,
so after 7 days it took a day or two for the
claim etc. to be made
and I will show you what all
changes have happened in it, look, this has changed in our front, the
entire indicator has changed, its
mudguard has changed,
its tank start has also
changed, its end, its leg guard, this has also changed, it has a grab rail, this is also
brand new, its
handle bar has also changed, so
now let's talk in detail
about the insurance claim of your bike, see friend, last time I
came here last Sunday to deposit the bike, last
Monday  I had come and today
is Monday, it was completely a week yesterday
and within one week the entire work on the bike etc. was done and
look at me friend, if I
tell you, look, I am telling you honestly, the
process was quite smooth and as many times as I
mean I visited many times in between,
you must have also seen the clips in it, then
you must have seen yourself that the transparency
between the customer and the vendor was quite
good, I monitored all the processes of this,
whatever parts etc. were changed in it,
I monitored them all properly, so
look, I will show you what all
changes have happened in it, this left
part of the visor has been changed,
its headlight inside it is burnt, it is
absolutely brand new, its mudguard has been
changed and its shower had got bent, so
this one was
slightly straightened by going to the machine and
again and the most major
expense of this is its alloy, its entire alloy has been
changed, its old alloy was slightly bent
here  It had got bent
after the crash, along with that its leg guard has also been
changed, our left
tank strut, look at the tank, the
tank in Apache
comes in three parts, there are two struts
inside it and in the middle is our
fuel tank, this
left strut of it was damaged, along with that the
small grab rail at the back has also been changed
and yes one more thing I did
not forget to tell you is its handle bar,
inside it you get clip on handle
bars, so our left handle in it was
also broken, it had got slightly bent due to
which this part of ours also got damaged, so this
part has also been changed, see there was a
major expense inside the bike and here I have the
invoice, let me show you how much has been
spent and how much have I paid,
so look these are all the add ons that have been
changed in it, here is our
tank cover, this is the tank cover, damper, leg guard,
fender, black lever, our lever has
also changed, our headlamp has also been changed  There
is housing, handle bar, grip, all these
things are inside it and this is its
total amount and the total expense incurred is
₹1,717, so we have spent ₹1,717,
but how much have we paid
because we are first party insurance
people, in this I have spent
₹5000000
recharge and 1700 1717,
I got it laced a little and it was
around 16,611, what
happens in this, see, in the ICICI Lambadi
policy, in the
first claim you make,
your company pays 90% and
you have to pay 10%, so it cost approximately ₹1,
if we calculate its % then it is approximately
₹10,00000, if we add its file charge, then
its bill is around ₹20,00000, so yes, it is around
₹20,00000  Our bike is completely
ready inside, isn't it, which is a very
good thing, I mean my main concern was that the
bike's movement should not be affected, that is, the
alignment etc. should not be affected
because what happens is that whenever a bike meets with a
crash, etc., then its steering gets bent,
but I have ridden the bike properly and there is
no problem in it as of now, the bike is
running in a straight line, so the initial
clips were from the end of last Monday, which
is our second Monday, so it has taken
us completely one week to get the entire bike repaired, etc., etc.,
okay, so let's do
a motor blog and let's talk about the rest, let's go
to the motor blog once, and
now see, I have one more most
important work to be done in this, do you know what it is, as
you guys know, look, I had got the
entire lamination done on this bike earlier, so
now all the parts that have been changed,
now they are completely done, so
now these ones  I need to get the lamination done on this part, it will be done
after some time. I am having a
slight problem with it. The bike is
not looking too vibrant, a little bit.
Now it looks normal to me. Rest, all the
updates that have been coming from time to time have come to me
through messages. So it's fine. You know, the
reviews of TVs are
not good online. People online criticize the
TVs a lot, saying the quality is
very bad. But in my case, it's
fine. They did the service well too, they
treat me
well and they do the work quickly.
And one week
is not a big time, it's not a long time,
right? One week is very less time.
I have seen people's cars parked for a month, even then
their work is not
completed. In fact, look inside it, there were major
parts, there was the headlight, there was the front alloy wheel, there was the
tank rout, I mean, look, there were major
works.  No, it was a small job, so look,
here the question arises that how the
company arranges the parts, I
found it to be fine, I will give a good review, otherwise,
look, no one is
spoiling me, your brother has not yet become so big
that people spoil him, look,
I will not talk with any company bias, I will
talk as a customer, and
look, I told you earlier that
whenever you take insurance etc.,
what documents do you have to provide, you have to provide
your owner's PAN
card, Aadhar card and DL, you have to provide the person in
whose name the vehicle is,
right? And when we
buy our vehicle, at that time you just have to
show them, show all those documents
once so that they can verify that the person
who gave the bike is coming to take it, right?
And yes, there is one more thing, for example, suppose
I have this ICICI Bank first
party insurance for one year, so
what happens in this is that in one year,
you get two claims in one year, in
which you get only 10  But you will have to pay, the rest
of the 90% will be given by the company, that is, our
insurance company will pay, but if you claim for the third time, then
you will have to pay
50%, that is, you will
pay 50%, the company will pay, so this is their policy,
if seen under the first party, then it is
something like this, otherwise,
we get a third party cover for 4 years, which we have got
from the company,
okay,
yes, the rest of the bike is running
smoothly, no
problems, so look, we have come again to the
same shop where we had got
our lamination done here earlier, so look, it is
necessary to get PPF done on these as well, our entire
bike is already covered, I mean the vehicle is covered, there is no
problem, so today let's get these parts done as well,
first of all, see, the
wrap that comes from the company, let's remove it, oh,
okay, and it is not a time consuming job, it will take
two minutes, this
too, child
[Music]
these are all the old parts, let me show you
what it is,
look, first of all, it is our alloy here, let me
show you
what was damaged in it  Brother, look, this was the major
damage due to which our alloy has
changed. Here is our rear
grab rail. This is our tank route, left
tank route. The old one, its name was here. Here is
our mud guard. The second
most expensive part is our
headlight. Here are our headlights. We will not
do any modification on this. This is our
side mask and this is
our headlight housing. This is another one. This is
our clip on because one handle bar of
this has been changed. Here is the leg guard and
one more thing. This is our lever. Okay, so
guys, this was all about the box. Is there anything else?
And look, all this stuff has come out of
ours. So, take care of these things.
Whenever you make your claim etc., the
old parts are yours.
Go and tell them that brother, I
need our parts and take them. If
you need them, you can use them.
We will use them because we do some
experiment or the other, that's why we will
use them.  This alloy of ours,
this alloy is also going to be very useful,
okay, let's keep it in this video, I
hope you liked the video and
tell me how you liked the information that I have given you,
I have squeezed the entire journey into just one video, so
tell me how you liked it, till then we will meet
in the next video, bye bye